{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "General%20Knowledge",
            "type": "boolean",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Gumbo%20is%20a%20stew%20that%20originated%20in%20Louisiana.",
            "correct_answer": "True",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "False"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "On%20which%20computer%20hardware%20device%20is%20the%20BIOS%20chip%20located%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Motherboard",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Hard%20Disk%20Drive",
                "Central%20Processing%20Unit",
                "Graphics%20Processing%20Unit"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Film",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20James%20Bond%20villains%20is%20not%20affiliated%20with%20the%20SPECTRE%20organization%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Auric%20Goldfinger",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Dr.%20Julius%20No",
                "Rosa%20Klebb",
                "Emilio%20Largo"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "In%20Call%20of%20Duty%3A%20United%20Offensive%2C%20what%20two%20soldiers%20share%20a%20name%20of%20a%20video%20game%20character%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Gordon%20%26%20Freeman",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Sam%20%26%20Fisher",
                "Nathan%20%26%20Drake",
                "Dig%20%26%20Dug"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "In%20Danganronpa%3A%20Trigger%20Happy%20Havoc%2C%20what%20is%20the%20protagonist%27s%20name%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Makoto%20Naegi",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Hajime%20Hinata",
                "Nagito%20Komaeda",
                "Komaru%20Naegi"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Geography",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What%20is%20the%20tallest%20mountain%20in%20Canada%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Mount%20Logan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Mont%20Tremblant",
                "Whistler%20Mountain",
                "Blue%20Mountain"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What%20team%20won%20the%202016%20MLS%20Cup%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Seattle%20Sounders",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Colorado%20Rapids",
                "Toronto%20FC",
                "Montreal%20Impact"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The%20character%20Plum%20from%20%22No%20Game%20No%20Life%22%20is%20of%20what%20race%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Dhampir",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Fl%C3%BCgel",
                "Imanity",
                "Seiren"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "The%20character%20Momonga%20from%20the%20%22Overlord%22%20series%20orders%20his%20servants%20to%20call%20him%20by%20what%20name%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Ainz%20Ooal%20Gown",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Master",
                "Yggdrasil",
                "Kugane%20Maruyama"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "Sports",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which%20boxer%20was%20banned%20for%20taking%20a%20bite%20out%20of%20Evander%20Holyfield%27s%20ear%20in%201997%3F",
            "correct_answer": "Mike%20Tyson",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Roy%20Jones%20Jr.",
                "Evander%20Holyfield",
                "Lennox%20Lewis"
            ]
        }
    ]
}
